What time is it now?
كم الوقت الان؟
Ah,
آه،
Some people are afraid of losing,
بعض الناس يخافون من الخسارة ،
so they dare not come.
لذلك لا يجرؤون على المجيء.
Am I right?
هل انا على حق؟
Are you scared?
هل انت خائف؟
Who said we didn't dare to come?
من قال أننا لم نجرؤ على المجيء؟
Who is this?
من هذا؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Dressed like this,
يرتدون مثل هذا ،
It's immoral.
إنه أمر غير أخلاقي.
Does it look good?
هل تبدو جيدة؟
I think it's pretty good.
وأعتقد أن لها جيدة.
It's a game you can't win.
إنها لعبة لا يمكنك الفوز بها.
Do you have to come?
هل عليك المجيء؟
I was thinking,
كنت افكر،
Shopkeeper Chen,
صاحب متجر تشين ،
If I don't scold you every day,
إذا لم أؤنبك كل يوم ،
you'll feel uncomfortable.
ستشعر بعدم الارتياح.
If you lose the game,
إذا خسرت اللعبة ،
you can't be scolded by me anymore.
لا يمكنك توبيخك من قبلي بعد الآن.
I'm not used to it,
انا لست معتاد عليه،
You,
أنت،
It's okay.
انه بخير.
What about today?
ماذا عن اليوم؟
I'd like to give you a few words as a gift.
أود أن أقدم لك بضع كلمات كهدية.
I'll make you happy.
سوف تجعلك سعيدا.
Beep! Beep! Beep! Beep! Beep! Beep! Beep! Beep! Beep!
زمارة!  زمارة!  زمارة!  زمارة!  زمارة!  زمارة!  زمارة!  زمارة!  زمارة!
Beep! You dare to bully Juan.
زمارة!  أنت تجرؤ على التنمر على خوان.
Sooner or later,
عاجلا أم آجلا،
you have to be beeping.
عليك أن تكون صفير.
Gosh,
يا الهي ،
I'll go.
سأذهب.
The rules of today's competition are very simple,
قواعد مسابقة اليوم بسيطة للغاية ،
two models show their clothes
نموذجان يعرضان ملابسهما
on the stage respectively,
على المسرح على التوالي ،
The winner is decided by the applause
يتم تحديد الفائز بالتصفيق
and screams of the audience.
وصراخ الجمهور.
Now,
الآن،
let's start the competition.
لنبدأ المنافسة.
Okay,
تمام،
Okay.
تمام.
It looks good.
إن شكلها جيد.
Okay,
تمام،
Nice.
لطيف.
It looks good.
إن شكلها جيد.
Okay,
تمام،
They're going to win.
سوف يفوزون.
Shopkeeper Chen,
صاحب متجر تشين ،
is there any need to compete in this situation?
هل هناك حاجة للمنافسة في هذه الحالة؟
You fat people are cheap people
أنتم السمان أناس رخيصون
who wear beautiful clothes,
الذين يرتدون ملابس جميلة ،
Unseemly,
غير لائق
Let's go.
هيا بنا.
When I first met Juan,
عندما قابلت خوان لأول مرة ،
she was being bullied by two bad guys.
كانت تتعرض للتخويف من قبل اثنين من الأشرار.
She didn't dare to resist.
لم تجرؤ على المقاومة.
There was no other reason.
لم يكن هناك سبب آخر.
Because she's fat.
لأنها سمينة.
She didn't do anything wrong.
لم ترتكب أي خطأ.
On the contrary,
على العكس تماما،
she is a kind and beautiful girl.
إنها فتاة لطيفة وجميلة.
Then why are you being treated unfairly
إذن لماذا يتم التعامل معك بشكل غير عادل
because you're fat?
لانك سمين؟
Just because of that weird rule?
فقط بسبب تلك القاعدة الغريبة؟
All men are created equal.
كل البشر خلقوا متساويين.
Whether we are fat or thin,
سواء كنا سمينين أو نحيفين ،
we all have the right to pursue good things.
لدينا جميعًا الحق في السعي وراء الأشياء الجيدة.
All of us should stand up bravely
يجب علينا جميعا أن نقف بشجاعة
and advocate the concept of equality,
والدعوة لمفهوم المساواة ،
Well said,
احسنت القول،
Okay,
تمام،
Well said.
احسنت القول.
Well said,
احسنت القول،
Okay,
تمام،
I should learn from her.
يجب أن أتعلم منها.
People,
الناس،
All men are created equal,
كل البشر خلقوا متساويين،
Okay,
تمام،
That's how it should be.
هذا هو ما ينبغي أن يكون.
Su Jinxia,
سو جينشيا ،